<Tutorial description="This tutorial is about the crafting system">
	<Start type="text">
		<Content>
		Welcome to the Crafing Tutorial.
		It will explain StarMade's
		crafting and factory system.
		</Content>
		<Duration>3000</Duration>
		<Satisfied>StateA</Satisfied>
	</Start>
	
	<StateA type="text">
		<Content>
		Crafting in StarMade is based on a "consistence" system.
		Every craftable element has an amount of
		other elements it is made from. These other
		elements again have other elements they are
		made off and so forth.
		You can compare this system with a tree that has branches.
		</Content>
		<Duration>3000</Duration>
		<Back>Start</Back>
		<Satisfied>StateB</Satisfied>
	</StateA>
	
	
	<StateB type="text">
		<Content>
		Consistence trees do not loop, so
		an element (the tree's root) is never in any
		of the branches of its own crafting tree.
		</Content>
		<Duration>3000</Duration>
		<Back>StateA</Back>
		<Satisfied>StateC</Satisfied>
	</StateB>
	
	<StateC type="text">
		<Content>
		The other system is using recipes.
		Recipes just determine fixed product lines.
		
		For example: 10 of any ore capsule makes a meta mesh.
		</Content>
		<Duration>3000</Duration>
		<Back>StateB</Back>
		<Satisfied>StateD</Satisfied>
	</StateC>
	
	<StateD type="text">
		<Content>
		Enough theory for now. Here is how you start
		with absolutely nothing but your initial
		personal power beam.
		</Content>
		<Duration>3000</Duration>
		<Back>StateC</Back>
		<Satisfied>StateE</Satisfied>
	</StateD>
	
	<StateE type="text">
		<Content>
		StarMade's raw resources exist in two groups:
		Crystal shards and ores. Each planet part
		has two random resources, while the resources
		on asteroids are set per type. You'll find 
		different types of asteroids depending on
		the distance between the sector and the star.	
		</Content>
		<Duration>3000</Duration>
		<Back>StateD</Back>
		<Satisfied>StateF</Satisfied>
	</StateE>
	
	<StateF type="text">
		<Content>
		To start, collect some raw ore by salvaging 
		some resources with a basic ship or as astronaut.
		After you've done that, open your inventory with $INVENTORY_PANEL and click the
		'Craft Capsule' button. This will open your personal 
		capsule factory. You can also craft a factory block
		that is faster and more efficient.		
		</Content>
		<Duration>3000</Duration>
		<Back>StateE</Back>
		<Satisfied>StateG</Satisfied>
	</StateF>
	
	<StateG type="text">
		<Content>
		Put one type of shards or ores in it and leave
		the second slot empty (the processed product will use this slot). 
		After a short time, you should be
		getting a lot of capsules from that type.
		Place those in your inventory.		
		</Content>
		<Duration>3000</Duration>
		<Back>StateF</Back>
		<Satisfied>StateG1</Satisfied>
	</StateG>
	
	<StateG1 type="text">
		<Content>
		You can click on the 'Production' button
		to check which raw resource will produce
		which capsule.		
		</Content>		
		<Duration>3000</Duration>
		<Back>StateG</Back>
		<Satisfied>StateH</Satisfied>
	</StateG1>
	
	<StateH type="text">
		<Content>
		After you made some capsules, click on
		the 'Micro' button in your inventory and place
		them there. You need 10 capsules of any(!)
		type to produce either metal meshes (ore capsules),
		or circuits (shard capsules).
		Those two are the base ingredients for most of
		the blocks in StarMade.		
		</Content>
		<Duration>3000</Duration>
		<Back>StateG</Back>
		<Satisfied>StateI</Satisfied>
	</StateH>
	
	<StateI type="text">
		<Content>
		When you have either 20 metal meshes or circuits,
		press on the 'craft macro' button to craft your first macro
		factory. The macro factory makes every craftable
		block in the game. You can only place this block
		on a station or a planet.
		</Content>		
		<Duration>3000</Duration>
		<Back>StateH</Back>
		<Satisfied>StateI1</Satisfied>
	</StateI>
	
	<StateI1 type="text">
		<Content>
		After you placed a macro factory you will see
		that it needs power to function. You can provide
		that power by shooting it with your personal power
		supply beam, or if you have them, placing down
		power recharge blocks. If you don't have any power blocks 
		then it	should focus to craft some in your new factory.
		</Content>
		<Duration>3000</Duration>
		<Back>StateI</Back>
		<Satisfied>StateJ</Satisfied>
	</StateI1>
	
	<StateJ type="text">
		<Content>
		Open the macro factory with $ACTIVATE and click on
		change production. You can use the filter and type
		for example 'power' to quickly find power modules
		in the drop down menu. After you chose the power recharge
		module, you can click on graph to see exactly
		what you need for making that block.
		</Content>
		<Image>powerRecipe</Image>
		<Duration>3000</Duration>
		<Back>StateI</Back>
		<Satisfied>StateK</Satisfied>
	</StateJ>
	
	<StateK type="text">
		<Content>
		IMPORTANT: The factory will only do the last step
		of the graph. Every step below that will require it's
		own factory. In this example the only thing that
		this factory will consume is Metal Mesh and 
		'Active Varat Processore', which you need to produce
		in a separate factory (or change the production on this one).
		</Content>
		<Image>factoryExp</Image>
		<Duration>3000</Duration>
		<Back>StateJ</Back>
		<Satisfied>StateL</Satisfied>
	</StateK>
	
	<StateL type="text">
		<Content>
		You can of course craft multiple factories
		to do all  these steps at once.
		
		Furthermore you are able to link factories:
		Press $SELECT_MODULE on the factory you want to be able
		to take needed materials out for other factories and
		press $CONNECT_MODULE on those to connect them with it.
		</Content>
		<Duration>3000</Duration>
		<Back>StateK</Back>
		<Satisfied>StateM</Satisfied>
	</StateL>
	
	<StateM type="text">
		<Content>
		A factory will take ingredients needed from
		all the factories that are connected to it.
		This basically enables you to rebuild a whole
		crafting tree. Then you can put in raw resources
		in the bottom and get the high level product on the top.
		</Content>
		<Duration>3000</Duration>
		<Back>StateL</Back>
		<Satisfied>End</Satisfied>
	</StateM>
	
	<End type="text">
		<Content>
		This concludes the Crafting Tutorial.
		Thanks for reading, and thanks for playing
		StarMade!
		</Content>
		<Duration>3000</Duration>
		<Back>Start</Back>
	</End>

</Tutorial>